# **Abodunrin Victoria**

# **Front End Developer**

Front End Developer with about a year of experience working with JavaScript, HTML/CSS, and React framework to deliver exceptional customer experiences. Adept at contributing to a highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions, and determining customer satisfaction.

Plot 7 off Sanda street Alegongo Estate, Akobo, Ibadan. 08134821529 victoriaoluwaferanmi@gmail.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Stutern Intern

# Front End Developer

March 2022 - Present

- Effective use of github for software development collaboration
- Developed web-apps based on figma design.
- Partnered with the UI/UX designers, back end developers while building the layout, functionalities and validations of the webpages.
- Participated in each step of the product development process from ideation to development improvement for features reaching users.
- Documentation and technical writing.

# SheCodeAfrica

## **UI/UX** Designer

March 2021 - June 2021

- Gained knowledge in UI/UX design fundamentals, understanding what users' requirement is and the importance of user research in design.
- Wireframing, user flows, user persona, mapping, prototyping and using mockups for designs and presentation of designs.
- Effective use of designs tools

### **Projects**

https://github.com/VictoriaOluwaferanmi

https://victoriaoluwaferanmi.medium.com/

#### **SKILLS**

Web Development

HTML

Css

Javascript

React

NextJs

Tailwind css

Bootstrap

Material Icon

FireBase

UI/UX

#### **EDUCATION**

# **University of Ibadan**

**Bsc.** Computer Science

2018 - date

University of Ibadan, Ibadan, Oyo state, Nigeria

### Polytechnic of Ibadan

OND. Computer Science

2015 - 2017

Polytechnic of Ibadan, Oyo state, Nigeria